I am convinced that you will find only one answer everywhere.
Do not speak of guests and do not speak of symbolic trade, but rather of peace.
That is the wish of the people.
If this Sunday speaks to me of this great trust of the German people,
and legitimizes me again as the speaker of the nation,
and with that I am justified to say what I am explaining here,
that Germany is explaining, that the German people is explaining.
We have become such a decent people again.
We have become such a hardworking and capable people again.
What can we not do again in Germany?
What do we not have for tasks?
We have been told all these years that the German people are not quite equal to the other peoples in the world.
What do we have for tasks today?
What great works are we building?
We are building the most beautiful streets today,
huge facilities, industrial art, new inventions we have made,
enormous residential colonies.
They are being created and have already been created.
What is not being worked on everywhere, in all areas?
We have proven in these three years that we are a people that can stand up to others.
And that is why I am asking you, German people,
to give your verdict.
I do not submit to the world.
It cannot judge me.
I submit to you.
Do you judge me?
Do you give me a confession if you think my work is right?
Do you think that I have been hardworking, that I have worked,
that I have not used myself for you in these years,
that I have used my time well in the service of my people?
Do you give me a vote now?
If yes, then step in for me as I step in for you.